<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Flippit</string>
    <string name="activity_launcher_title">Flippit</string>
    <string name="activity_settings_title">Settings</string>
    <string name="activity_howToPlay_title">How to Play</string>
    <string name="action_new_game">New Game</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_howtoplay">How to Play</string>
    <string name="player1_label_default">Player 1</string>
    <string name="player2_label">Computer</string>
    <string name="bad_move">Error: Invalid Move</string>
    <string name="no_moves">No moves for </string>
	<string name="winner_p1">You win.</string>
	<string name="winner_cpu">CPU wins.</string>
	<string name="winner_none">No winner.</string>
    <string name="button_start_1p">Single Player</string>
    <string name="button_start_mp">Multiplayer</string>
    <string name="coming_soon">Coming Soon</string>

	<string name="pref_player_name_title">Player Name</string>
	<string name="pref_cat_ai">Computer AI</string>
	<string name="pref_ComputerAI_label">Enabled</string>
	<string name="pref_ai_difficulty">Difficulty</string>
	<string name="pref_ai_difficulty_def">Easy</string>

    <string name="how_to_play_p1_1">
        In Reversi there are two players, each represented by light or dark pieces on the game board.
        Players take turns laying pieces in order to capture spaces.
        The objective is to capture more spaces on the game board than your opponent.
    </string>

    <string name="how_to_play_p1_2">
        The game board is an 8x8 square, giving a total of 64 spaces in the entire board.
        The board is initialized with four pieces in the center four squares, alternating light and dark.
    </string>

    <string name="how_to_play_p2_1">
        On each move, a player must claim an empty space, so that there is at least one of their opponent\'s spaces in between the claimed space and one of their own spaces.
        After claiming a space, all of the opponent\'s spaces in between the claimed space and one of their own spaces are claimed by the player.
    </string>

    <string name="how_to_play_p2_2">
        If at any point in the game a player has no valid moves, the turn will be passed back to the other player.
        The game continues until neither player has any valid moves, or all spaces on the game board are claimed.
    </string>

    <string name="how_to_play_p3">
        A good starting strategy for Reversi is to focus on claiming "stable" spaces, for which all of the adjacent spaces are of the same color,
        and therefore unable to be flanked for the rest of the game.
        Because of this, the four corner spaces are considered to be the most valuable, followed by spaces along the edges.
        Spaces immediately adjacent to the corners and edges should be avoided as these provide an opportunity for the opponent to claim stable spaces.
        For more information on the history of the game and basic strategy, see the Wikipedia page for Reversi.
    </string>

</resources>
